Today I start this challenge.
I will try to turn that R$1 into 1 deal in 30 days
think 1 cheaper thing.
Can the young man help me?
Is there anything you can buy with R$1 like that?
2 pieces to sell tastes like R$1 2 paçoquinha and let's
start this saga that I can do today,
let's go to this ass.
You will see me a lot here today.
If God wants you to play,
beat here.
I think I'll talk to you that this.
You look happy.
All good get out of here even Yasmin let me tell you.
If you want a paçoquinha help you fix your day have something more happy.
Alright people everything good here just a second worth it.
Man.
My first real bro.
Hi brother thanks can I post?
It was
6 paçoca gives 3 real 3 real Breno here just
bought a paçoca man you sent ten real.
Oh no brother thank you so much brother caraca old I won ten reais.
I'm in a little hurry.
Imagine last day there everything good was worth it
is difficult Guy only 1 minute was not worth it.
If they're drinking coffee here,
you asked me not to film,
I won't film and thank you so much.
It didn't but it was good people.
You have to find the right person.
If you connect it's on but it's time for you to take some out so bro it's really
in the face so from the can you have more this one I wanted two I have
caraca mano I'm going to buy paçoca mano again
see you in a little while.
People Júlio here,
guys,
Nicolas here,
already adding to the project and bro,
let's go.
I just sold four paçoca for ten reais the guy said bro take it then véi gave me
ten thousand cara ou que cavalinho has a great day there from the heart.
A good week.
I don't even know how much got in here.
Let me take a look.
I started this with a real one and now I want to show you how much I did today.
10 15 20 25 39 60 53reals in pix.
That was the one of thirty and tomorrow I come up with a new idea.
If you want to see how far this goes,
join me there.
Closed tamo together.